All right. So, here's my solution for this exercise.
好了这是习题答案视频
So, here, I had you calculate the output of
在这道题里 我们要使用
this multi-layer network using the weights and features that we've defined up here.
在这里定义的 weights 和 features 计算这个多层网络的输出
So, it was really similar to what we did before with
流程和之前的单层神经网络
our single layer simple neural network.
很相似
So, it's basically just taking the features and our weight matrix,
传入 features 和权重矩阵
our first weight matrix,
即第一个权重矩阵
and calculating a matrix multiplication.
进行矩阵乘法运算
So, here's the torch.mm plus B1,
这是 torch.mm + b1
and then that gives us values for our hidden layer H. Now,
获得隐藏层 h 的值
we can use the values H as the input for the next layer of our network.
现在我们可以使用值 h
So, we just do, again,
作为网络下一层级的输入
a matrix multiplication of these hidden values H,
用这些隐藏值 h 与
with our second weight matrix W2,
第二个权重矩阵 w2 进行矩阵乘法运算
and adding on our bias terms, and then we get the output.
加上偏差项 得出输出
So, my favorite features of PyTorches is being able to
PyTorch 能够
convert between Numpy arrays and Torch tensors,
轻松实现
in a very nice and easy manner.
在 NumPy 数组和 Torch 张量之间的转换
So, this is really useful because a lot of the times,
这样很方便 因为很多时候
you'll be preparing your data and to do some preprocessing using Numpy,
你需要使用 NumPy 准备和预处理数据
and then you want to move it into your network,
然后将数据传入网络中
and so, you have to bridge these Numpy arrays,
因此 你需要
what you're using for your data,
在数据所采用的 NumPy 数组
and then the Torch tensors that you're using for your network.
和网络所使用的 Torch 张量之间建立联系
So, actually, to do this,
所以
we can actually get a tensor from a Numpy array using torch.fromnumpy.
我们可以使用 torch.from_numpy 从 NumPy 数组中获取张量
So, here I've just created a random array, a four-by-three array,
我在这里创建了一个 4x3 随机数组
and then we can create a Torch tensor from
然后通过该数组创建一个 Torch 张量
this array just by doing.from Numpy, and passing an array.
方法是调用 .from_numpy 并传入数组
So, this creates a nice tensor for us.
这样就能为我们创建张量
So, this is a tensor in PyTorch,
这就是 PyTorch 中的张量
we can use with all of our Torch methods and eventually,
我们可以对其使用各种 Torch 方法
use it in a neural network.
并最终用在神经网络里
Then, we can go backwards,
还可以反过来
so we can take a tensor such as B here.
我们可以传入一个张量
This is our Torch tensor and we can go back to a Numpy array doing b.numpy.
例如这里的 Torch 张量 b
So, this gives us back our Numpy array.
并使用 b.numpy 将其转回 NumPy 数组
So, one thing to remember when you're doing this,
要注意的一点是
is that the memory is actually shared between the Numpy array and this Torch tensor.
内存会在 NumPy 数组和这个 Torch 张量之间共享
So, what this means, is that if you do any operations in
也就是说 如果你对 NumPy 数组或张量
place on either the Numpy array or the tensor,
执行任何原地操作
then you're going to change the values for the other one.
就会更改对方的值
So, for example, if we do this in-place operation of multiplying by two,
例如 如果我们原地乘以 2
which means that we're actually changing the values in memory,
意味着我们将更改内存中的值
and not creating a new tensor,
并且不创建新的张量
then we will actually change the values in the Numpy array.
那么我们就会更改 NumPy 数组中的值
So, you see here, we have our Numpy array.
这是我们的 NumPy 数组
So initially, it's like this,
一开始是这样的
convert it to a Torch tensor, and here,
将其转换为 Torch 张量
I'm doing this in-place multiplication,
在这里进行原地乘法运算
and we've changed our values for this tensor.
更改了这个张量的值
Then, if you look back at the Numpy array,
再回来看看 NumPy 数组
the values have changed.
发现值变了
So, that's just something to keep in mind as you're doing this,
在进行转换时要注意这一点
so you're not caught off guard when you're seeing your arrays,
这样的话 当你对张量进行操作时
your Numpy arrays, being changed because of operations you're doing on the tensor.
发现 NumPy 数组也改变了不会吓一跳
See you in the next video, cheers.
下个视频见！